intermatwrestle.com 2003-06-11

# Privacy Statement for InterMat Wrestling

## Privacy Statement for InterMat Wrestling

InterMat Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: InterMat Wrestling.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart in the InterMat Wrestling Store. We also use per-session cookies to save your Premium Service Identification so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit a new page within Premium Service.

This site contains links to other sites. **InterMat Wrestling** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

Our online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. _For information regarding the Flycast Advertising's privacy policy, please go to<http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>._

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our Security Certificate is provided by [Thawte.](http://www.thawte.com/)

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. Please send an email to [support@intermatwrestle.com](mailto:support@intermatwrestle.com) regarding the information you received from InterMat.

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Please send an email to [support@intermatwrestle.com](mailto:support@intermatwrestle.com) regarding which information you would like updated.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Tom Owens InterMat Inc. 5650 NW Johnston Dr Suite B Johnston, IA 50131 [tom@intermatwrestle.com](mailto:tom@intermatwrestle.com) (515) 276-6679
